Welcome to AI Agents in LineDraft, built in partnership with LineChain
and Tuvelli, taught by Harrison Chase, co-founder and CEO of LineChain, as well
as Droughton Vice, who is co-founder and CEO of Tuvelli. Harrison, it was not
quite a year ago that we're working on our first course on OM Frameworks and
back then, we had an agent example, but you know, it was a little bit of a
struggle to get it to work. Since then, I've seen many teams successfully built
AI agents. What was your view on that? Yeah, that's exactly right, Andrew. We've
seen many people successfully building agentic applications now, and I think
there were a couple of key improvements over the last year. First, function
calling alums have made tool use much more predictable and stable, and also
specific tools like search have been adapted for agentic use. Yes, if you think
about it, when you do a aquarium search engine, it will return multiple links that
you can then follow to find answers. However, what an agent really wants or
answered that you can then reference to the link. Also, the agent needs
predictable format for its results. This is exactly what agentic search provides.
That makes sense, and by the way, I'm personally a user of LineChain and Langsworth
and to the reason for the excitement of both of you here. And let me start by
describing agents and agentic workflows. Let's say that the fee of us
are going to write a paper together. Maybe I will start with some planning and
try to put together an initial outline of the paper. Yeah, and I can take it
from there and do some research, maybe run some queries and compile documents
related to our topic. Okay, I guess that leaves me to write the first draft,
they hope it's not a long paper. Yeah, short paper, hopefully. And then after that,
I might read up the paper, try to make some constructors suggestions and hand it
back to Harrison to see if he wants to make some changes or the role terms to see if he
wants to do some more search and so on. And this would be an example of an
agentic or an agent like workflow in which we iterate to produce the word
product. And in contrast to how people often use LMS to write essays today,
which is to write a prompt and to write the essay from the first word to the
last word in one shot. This type of iterative workflow gives a much better
word product. In fact, as a person, I don't write that well. If you force me to
just write from start to finish with no backspacing allowed. So concretely, you
can similarly prompt an LM to tell it to write an outline, prompt an LM to write a
draft or revise it, prompt an LM to do search and so on. But to that with the
deeper, let me share what I think are the key design patterns of agentic
workflows. First, I think this planning, which is thinking through the steps to
take like the outline and what to do after that. Then to use knowing what
tools are available and how to use them like our search tool. Reflection, which
refers to iteratively improving a result, possibly with multiple LMS critiquing and
making useful suggestions to drive that type of editing cycle, multi-agent
communications. So you can think of each of us as playing a row akin to an LM with
a unique prompt to play a unique row in this process. And then memory that is
tracking the progress and results over the multiple steps. Now, some of these
capabilities are related to the LM itself, like function calling for two
years. But many of these capabilities are actually implemented outside the LM by
the framework that they operate in. Exactly. And the Langtrain framework has had
many of these elements for some time. Memory is available in multiple forms.
Supporting function calling, LMS and tool execution are available. And we talked
about this in the last deep learning class we did functions, tools and agents
course. But Langtrain has recently updated its support for agentic workflows. Here
are some examples of agents that we now better support. So react agents was an
early paradigm for building agents and reactants for reasoning and action. Another
example that we recently added support for is the example presented in the
self-refined paper where it does the iterative refinement that you were talking
about. And most recently, you can see the alphacodium example, which creates a
coding agent using flow engineering. And from all these diagrams, you can see
that these agents and their behavior is defined by a cyclical graph. And so to
support directly building agents like this, Langtrain has extended to support
Lang graph. In this course, you will start by building an agent from scratch with
just an alpham and Python. Then you'll learn about the components of Lang graph
by rebuilding that same agent using the Lang graph components directly.
Since search tools are such an important part of many agent applications, you
learned capabilities of agentic search and how to use it. There are two
additional capabilities that are helpful when building agents. First is being
able to receive human input. This allows you to guide an agent at critical
points. The second is persistence. This is the ability to store the current
state of information so that you can return to it later. This is great for both
debugging agents and for productionizing them. We will build a project using
Lang graph. But you'll have to reach the last lesson to figure out what it is.
And at the end, I'll describe some of the cool applications and future
directions I see for this technology. Many people have worked to create this
course. From Langtrain, I'd like to thank Lance Martin and Nuno Compos from
Tuvelli, Arsaf, Elovik, and from deepland.ai Jeff Lodzwey. All right, we don't
want to keep those agents waiting. Let's go on to the next video to get started.